Guide to the W. Sterling Cole papers M2023
Special Collections and University Archives, Colgate University Libraries
- TL Cole to Pastore, 1958 January 21; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 155)
- TLS Pastore to Cole, 1957 November 18; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 155)
- TLS Cole to Hoxter, 1957 November 5; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 155)
- TL Cole to Walter A. Hamilton, 1957 December 20; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 156)
- TL unknown secretary to Hamilton, 1957 October 14; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 156)
- TLS Hamilton to Cole, 1957 October 14; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 156)
- TLS Menke to Cole, 1957 October 14; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 157)
- TLS Jerome A. Lederman to Cole, 1957 December 12; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 157)
- TL Cole to Menke, 1957 December 20; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 157)
- TL Cole to Jerome A. Lederman, 1958 January 17; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 157)
- TL Cole to Arthur J. Ford, 1957 December 11; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 158)
- TLS Arthur J. Ford to Cole, 1957 December 2; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 158)
- Telegram Hugh G. Elbot to Cole, 1957 December 1 (Box 3, Folder 158)
- TL Cole to Honorable Warren M. Anderson, 1957 December 20; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 159)
- TLS Warren Anderson to Cole, 1957 December 2; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 159)
- TL Cole to Robert Cleveland Holland, 1957 December 11; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 159)
- TL Cole to Mr. Philippe de Seynes, 1957 December 20; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 160)
- TL unknown secretary to Mr. Philipe de Seynes, 1957 October 24; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 160)
- TLS Seynes to Cole, 1957 October 11; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 160)
- TL Cole to John J. Horey Esq., 1957 December 20; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 161)
- TLS John Horey to Cole, 1957 December 2; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 161)
- TL Cole to AJ Hamilton, 1957 December 20; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 161)
- TLS AJ Hamilton to Cole, 1957 November 22; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 161)
- TL Cole to Dr. George H. Allen, Jr., 1957 December 21; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 162)
- TL unknown secretary to George Allen, Jr., 1957 October 24; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 162)
- TLS George Allen, Jr. to Cole, 1957 October 12; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 162)
- TL Cole to Rear Admiral W.F. Gentner, Jr., 1957 December 21; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 163)
- TL unknown secretary to WE Gentner, Jr., 1957 October 30; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 163)
- TLS W.E. Gentner, Jr. to Cole, 1957 October 14; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 163)
- TL Cole to Raymond K. Appleyard, 1957 December 21; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 164)
- TL unknown secretary to Raymond K. Appleyard, 1957 October 14; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 164)
- TLS Appleyard to Cole, 1957 October 18; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 164)
- TL Cole to Philip H. Willkie, 1957 November 23; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 165)
- TLS Philip H. Willkie to Cole, 1957 November 7; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 165)
- TL Cole to Senor Eduardo Hernandez Vidal, 1957 October 29; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 165)
- TLS Eduardo Hernandez Vidal to Cole, 1957 October 21; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 165)
- TL Cole to Dr. R.G.H. Siu, 1957 November 1; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 166)
- TLS RGH SIU to Cole, 1957 October 21; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 166)
- TLS A.I. Milstein to Cole, 1957 October 25; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 166)
- AN Kohn to Cole, undated; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 167)
- TLS Estes Kefauver to Cole, 1957 October 24; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 167)
- TLS William H. Eells to Cole, 1957 October 24; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 167)
- AN Ruth Bale to Cole, 1957 October 18; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 168)
- AN Judi Parder to Cole, 1957 October 7; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 168)
- TLS Mrs. Eugene Blystone to Cole, 1957 October 9; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 168)
- TL Cole to A.S. Mike Monroney, 1957 October 21; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 169)
- Telegram Mike Munroney to Cole, 1957 October 5; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 169)
- Radiogram JCAE staff to Cole, undated; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 169)
- AN Jary to Cole, 1957 October 8; 4 pp. (Box 3, Folder 170)
- TLS Alma G. Butler to Cole, 1957 October 9; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 170)
- TLS James Fulton to Cole, 1957 October 19; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 170)
- TLS George Dondero to Cole, 1957 October 17; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 171)
- AN Kathryn M. Williams to Cole, 1957 October 5; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 171)
- TLS F.P. Ellinger to Cole, 1957 October 11; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 171)
- TL Cole to Robert I. Hood, 1957 October 21; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 172)
- TLS Robert I. Hood to Cole, 1957 October 8; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 172)
- TLS William F. Daniels to Cole, 1957 October 22; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 172)
- TLS A. Fernos-Isern to Cole, 1957 October 23; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 173)
- TLS Ephram Martin to Cole, 1957 October 22; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 173)
- TLS William A. Lyons to Cole, 1957 October 21; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 173)
- TLS Marne Obernauer to Cole, 1957 October 8; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 174)
- AN Joshua Morrison to Cole, undated; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 174)
- Newspaper Article "Atomic Needler", 1957 October 7; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 174)
- TLS Andrew W. Knebel to Cole, 1957 October 22; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 175)
- TLS Wilbur E. Hammaker, 1957 October 12; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 175)
- TLS Robert C. Sprague to Cole, 1957 October 16; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 175)
- TLS William A. Consodine to Cole, 1957 October 15; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 176)
- AN Ray W. Brown to Cole, 1957 October 18; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 176)
- TLS KE Fields to Cole, 1957 October 17; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 176)
- TLS James F. Corby to Cole, 1957 October 15; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 177)
- TLS Clifford G. McIntire to Cole, 1957 October 15; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 177)
- TLS William Springer to Cole, 1957 October 16; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 177)
- TLS Thomas D. White to Cole, 1957 October 14; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 178)
- TL Thomas D. White to Cole, 1957 October 14; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 178)
- TLS Robert McManus to Cole, 1957 October 14; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 178)
- TLS Kenneth B. Keating to Cole, 1957 October 14; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 179)
- TLS O.S. Colclough to Cole, 1957 October 14; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 179)
- AN Margaret Taylor to Cole, 1957 October 13; 2 pp. (Box 3, Folder 179)
- AN Paul Aull to Cole, 1957 October 13; 2 pp. (Box 3, Folder 180)
- TL Cole to Carl V. Nelson, 1957 October 30; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 180)
- TLS Carl Nelson to Cole, 1957 October 7; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 180)
- AN Mora and Harry Spaulding to Cole, undated (Box 3, Folder 181)
- Card, TLS Charles P. Nelson to Cole, 1957 October 17; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 181)
- TLS Josef Stein to Cole, 1957 October 17; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 181)
- TLS Chas A. Wolverton to Cole, 1957 October 16; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 181)
- TLS John Bricker to Cole, 1957 October 16; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 182)
- TLS Robert A. Grant to Cole, 1957 October 7; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 182)
- TLS John Davis Lodge to Cole, 1957 October 7; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 182)
- TLS Victor L. Anfuso to Cole, 1957 October 8; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 183)
- TLS WA Underhill to Cole, 1957 October 8; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 183)
- TLS Charles W. Perry to Cole, 1957 October 8; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 183)
- TLS Charles Martin to Cole, 1957 October 8; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 184)
- TLS Arleigh Burke to Cole, 1957 October 8; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 184)
- TLS William Davis, Jr. to Cole, 1957 October 9; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 184)
- TLS Bruch Babcock to Cole, 1957 October 10; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 185)
- TLS Secretary of the Navy to Cole, 1957 October 11; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 185)
- TLS Russell C. Stroup to Cole, 1957 October 11; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 185)
- TL Cole to Evelyn Summers, 1957 October 22; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 186)
- TLS Evelyn Summers to Cole, 1957 October 11; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 186)
- TLS Colgate W. Darden to Cole, 1957 October 10; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 186)
- TL Cole to Burdette Playfoot, 1957 October 22; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 187)
- TLS Burdette Playfoot to Cole, 1957 October 4; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 187)
- TL Cole to Jack Bauman, 1957 October 22; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 187)
- TLS Jack Bauman to Cole, 1957 October 3; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 187)
- TL Cole to Gordon K. Smith, 1957 October 22; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 188)
- TLS Gordon Smith to Cole, 1957 October 4; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 188)
- TL Cole to Lloyd E. Hoyt, 1957 October 22; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 188)
- AN Lloyd Hoyt to Cole, 1957 October 4; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 188)
- TL Cole to Howard J. Ludington, 1957 October 22; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 189)
- TLS Howard Ludington to Cole, 1957 October 7; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 189)
- TL Cole to Isidore Dollinger, 1957 October 22; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 189)
- TLS Isidore Dollinger to Cole, 1957 October 7; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 189)
- TL Cole to Harold Moskovit, 1957 October 22; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 190)
- TLS Harold R. Moskovit to Cole, 1957 October 7; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 190)
- TL Cole to Charles C. Fichtner, 1957 October 22; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 190)
- TLS Charles C. Fichtner to Cole, 1957 October 7; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 190)
- TL Cole to Eugene J. Koegh, 1957 October 22; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 191)
- TLS Eugene Koegh to Cole, 1957 October 7; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 191)
- TL Cole to Leonard W. Hall, 1957 October 22; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 191)
- TLS Leonard W. Hall to Cole, 1957 October 8; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 191)
- TL Cole to William Borden, 1957 October 22; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 192)
- TLS William Borden to Cole, 1957 October 8; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 192)
- TLS A.R. Towner to Cole, 1957 October 8; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 192)
- TL Cole to A.R. Towner, 1957 October 22; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 192)
- TL Cole to William B. Goat, 1957 October 22; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 193)
- TLS William B. Goat to Cole, 1957 October 8; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 193)
- TL Cole to Clifford White, 1957 October 22; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 193)
- TLS Clifford White to Cole, 1957 October 8; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 193)
- TL Cole to Alfred P. Ilch, 1957 October 22; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 194)
- TLS Alfred Ilch to Cole, 1957 October 8; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 194)
- TL Cole to CH Green, 1957 October 22; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 194)
- TLS Charles H. Green to Cole, 1957 October 8; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 194)
- TL Cole to Lawrence H. Smith, 1957 October 22; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 195)
- Telegram Lawrence H. Smith to Cole, 1957 October 8; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 195)
- TL Cole to Frank L. Sundstrom, 1957 October 22; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 195)
- TLS Frank Sundstrom to Cole, 1957 October 8; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 195)
- TL Cole to Admiral E.E. Stephan, 1957 October 22; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 196)
- TLS E.C. Stephan to Cole, 1957 October 8; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 196)
- TL Cole to Lee D. Miller, 1957 October 22; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 196)
- TLS Lee D. Miller to Cole, 1957 October 8; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 196)
- TL Cole to Richard W. Webb, 1957 October 22; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 197)
- AN Richard W. Webb to Cole, undated; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 197)
- TL Cole to Sites, 1957 October 21; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 197)
- TLS James N. Sites to Cole, 1957 October 8; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 197)
- TL Cole to Barron, 1957 October 21; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 197)
- AN Blakeslee Barron to Cole, 1957 October 7; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 197)
- TLS Harold G. Mosier to Cole, 1957 October 9; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 198)
- TL Cole to Currie, 1957 October 22; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 198)
- TLS Lauchlin M. Currie to Cole, 1957 October 9; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 198)
- TL Cole to Hallauer, 1957 October 22; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 198)
- TLS Carl S. Hallauer to Cole, 1957 October 9; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 198)
- AN George McCullough to Cole, 1957 October 9; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 199)
- TLS Paul Seager to Cole, 1957 October 9; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 199)
- Telegram Joseph Campbell to Cole, 1957 October 9; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 199)
- AN Mrs. Sally Patchin Wayland to Cole, undated; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 200)
- TLS Ralph Harvey to Cole, 1957 October 9; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 200)
- TLS HE Orton to Cole, 1957 October 10; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 200)
- TLS Frederic R. Coudert, Jr. to Cole, 1957 October 10; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 201a)
- TLS Floyd Bryant to Cole, 1957 October 10; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 201a)
- TLS Maurice W. Fillius to Cole, 1957 October 11; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 201a)
- TLS Ted A. Ramsay to Cole, 1957 October 11; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 201b)
- TLS Charles E. Bennett to Cole, 1957 October 11; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 201b)
- AN Helen Dumack to Cole, 1957 October 12; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 201b)
- TLS George Abraham to Cole, 1957 October 15; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 202)
- TLS Maxwell Fassett to Cole, 1957 October 11; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 202)
- TLS Charles Adkins to Cole, 1957 October 15; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 202)
- TLS August Johansen to Cole, 1957 October 18; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 203)
- TLS Ernest H. Wakefield to Cole, 1957 October 15; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 203)
- TLS Melvin J. Maas to Cole, 1957 October 9; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 203)
- TLS Joseph J. Nasser to Cole, 1957 October 14; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 204)
- TLS Asher Lowich to Cole, 1957 October 16; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 204)
- TLS Dallas S. Townsend to Cole, 1957 October 17; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 204)
- TLS S.S. Auchincloss, 1957 October 17; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 205)
- TLS John Anderson to Cole, 1957 October 17; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 205)
- TLS W.E. Kelley to Cole, 1957 October 14; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 205)
- TLS Carroll D. Kearns to Cole, 1957 October 14; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 206)
- TLS Ed J. Smith to Cole, 1957 October 14; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 206)
- TL Cole to Nichols, 1957 October 21; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 206)
- TLS K.D. Nichols to Cole, 1957 October 8; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 206)
- TL Cole to Balcom, 1957 October 21; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 207)
- TLS Samuel B. Balcom to Cole, 1957 October 9; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 207)
- TL Cole to Christopher, Jr., 1957 October 21; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 207)
- TLS A.W. Christopher, Jr. to Cole, 1957 October 11; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 207)
- TL Cole to Weaver, 1957 October 21; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 207)
- TLS Charles H. Weaver to Cole, 1957 October 7; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 207)
- TL Cole to Persons, 1957 October 21; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 208)
- TLS Wilton B. Persons to Cole, 1957 October 14; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 208)
- TL Cole to Chernin, 1957 October 21; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 208)
- TLS Bernard H. Chernin to Cole, 1957 October 9; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 208)
- Radiogram Jose Ramon Quinones to Cole, 1957 October 9; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 208)
- TL Cole to Faber, 1957 October 21; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 209)
- Radiogram Mr. and Mrs. Faber to Cole, 1957 October; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 209)
- TL Cole to Bartolini, 1957 October 21; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 209)
- Radiogram Julian Bartolini to Cole, undated; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 209)
- TL Cole to Barr, 1957 October 21; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 209)
- Radiogram Eric Barr to Cole, 1957 October 22; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 209)
- TL Cole to Shugg, 1957 October 21; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 210)
- Radiogram Carleton Shugg to Cole, 1957 October 21; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 210)
- Radiogram the Moores to Cole, 1957 October; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 210)
- Radiogram Em and Lew to Cole, 1957 October; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 210)
- Radiogram Fred De Hoffmann to Cole, 1957 October; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 211)
- Radiogram Mary to Cole, 1957 October; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 211)
- Raiogram Winona and Fred Rhodes to Cole, 1957 October; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 211)
- Radiogram Bob and Ruth to Cole, 1957 October; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 212)
- Radiogram Mary to Cole, 1957 October; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 212)
- Radiogram Margaret and Jim to Cole, 1957 October; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 212)
- TLS Edith to Cole, 1957 October 7; 2 pp. (Box 3, Folder 213)
- TLS Lenoard Schwartz to Cole, 1957 October 7; 2 pp. (Box 3, Folder 213)
- TL White to Cole, 1957 October 15; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 213)
- TL Unknown sender to Cole, 1957 October 2; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 214)
- AN Jemy Wadsworth to Cole, undated; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 214)
- TLS Mary to Cole, undated; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 214)
- AN Seta to Cole, 1957 September 25; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 215)
- Radiogram Unknown sender to Cole, 1957 October; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 215)
- Radiogram Arthur Quinn to Cole, 1957 October; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 215)
- TLS Helena Higgins to Cole, 1957 October 7; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 216)
- Radiogram Unknown sender to Cole, 1957 October; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 216)
- TL Unknown Sender to Cole, 1957 October 9; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 216)
- TL Dulles to Cole, 1957 October 8; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 217)
- TLS S. Untermyer to Cole, 1957 September 17; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 217)
- TL Cole to S. Untermyer, 1957 September 23; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 217)
- TL Cole to Vernon E. Moore, 1957 September 16; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 218)
- TLS Vernon Moore to Cole, 1957 September 12; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 218)
- TLS Lindsay C. Warren to Cole, 1957 September 6; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 218)
- TL Cole to Lindsay Warren, 1957 September 10; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 218)
- TL Cole to Clarence E. Kilburn, 1957 September 10; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 219)
- TLS Clarence E. Kilburn to Cole, 1957 September 5; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 219)
- TL Cole to Karl Standish, 1957 September 10; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 219)
- TLS Karl Standish to Cole, undated; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 219)
- TL Cole to Jane Snader, 1957 September 5; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 220)
- AN Jane Snader to Cole, 1957 August 30; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 220)
- TLS Mr. Cammen to Cole, 1957 August 27; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 220)
- TL Cole to Matthew M. Cammen, 1957 September 4; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 220)
- TL Cole to Max Fine, 1957 September 5; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 221)
- TLS Max Fine to Cole, 1957 August 30; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 221)
- TL Cole to Mr. Charles J. Gilmore, 1957 September 4; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 221)
- AN Charles J. Fillmore to Cole, 1957 August 28; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 221)
- TL Cole to Allan Kenzie, 1957 September 4; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 222)
- AN Allan Kenzie to Cole, 1957 August 29; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 222)
- TL Cole to Rev. John Rainer Bodo, 1957 August 28; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 222)
- AN Rev. John Rainer Bodo to Cole, 1957 August 19; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 222)
- TLS Frank McCune to Cole, 1957 September 3; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 223)
- TL Cole to John Kenton, 1957 August 20; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 223)
- Telegram John Kenton to Cole, 1957 August 16; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 223)
- TL Cole to George McCullough, 1957 August 20; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 224)
- AN George McCullough to Cole, 1957 August 16; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 224)
- TL Cole to Alfred P. Ilch, 1957 August 20; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 224)
- TLS Alfred p. Ilch to Cole, 1957 August 16; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 224)
- TL Cole to Mr. J.K. Mansfield, 1957 August 20; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 225)
- TLS Mr. John Mansfield to Cole, 1957 August 16; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 225)
- TL Cole to Mr. Krishen D. Mathur, 1957 August 20; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 225)
- TLS Krishen Dayal Mathur to Cole, 1957 August 16; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 225)
- TL Cole to Arthur L. Quinn, 1957 August 20; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 226)
- AN Arthur L. Quinn to Cole, 1957 August 16; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 226)
- TL Cole to Mr. Lawrence E. Spivak, 1957 August 20; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 226)
- TLS Lawrence E. Spivak to Cole, 1957 August 17; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 226)
- TL Cole to Milton S. Kronheim, 1957 August 20; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 227)
- TLS Milton S. Kronheim to Cole, 1957 August 19; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 227)
- TLS Richard Mikeenan to Cole, 1957 November 1; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 227)
- TL Cole to Walter von Tresckow, 1957 September 4; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 228)
- TLS Walter von Tresckow to Cole, 1957 August 30; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 228)
- Pamphlet "Bulletin to the Schools" vol. 45, no. 7, 1959 March; Pg. 261-293 (Box 3, Folder 229)
- Biographical Information (Box 3, Folder 230)
- TLS Dr. Reinard Kamitz to Cole, 1961 October 31; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 231)
- TLS Canadian Representative to Cole, 1961 November 17; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 231)
- TLS Howard to Cole, 1961 November 9; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 231)
- Telegram Tom and Joan to Cole, 1961 November 23; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 232)
- TL Pavel Winkler to Cole, 1957 December 20; 3 pp. (Box 3, Folder 232)
- TLS Cole to Hill, 1959 June 22; 2 pp. (Box 3, Folder 233)
- TLS Cole to Hickenlooper, 1959 June 17; 1 p. (2 copies) (Box 3, Folder 233)
- Cole to Pastor, 1959 June 17; 1 p. (2 copies) (Box 3, Folder 233)
- TLS Cole to Scott, 1959 June 17; 2 pp. (2 copies) (Box 3, Folder 234)
- TLS Cole to Butler, 1959 June 17; 2 pp. (2 copies) (Box 3, Folder 234)
- TLS Tom Cole to Cole, 1956 December 25; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 234)
- TLS Cole to Scott, 1959 July 3; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 235)
- TLS Scott to Cole, 1959 June 24; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 235)
- TLS Scott to Anderson, 1959 June 24; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 235)
- TLS Scott to Cole, 1959 July 7; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 236)
- TLS Anderson to Scott, 1959 June 29; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 236)
- TLS Cole to Butler, 1959 June 29; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 236)
- TLS Mary to Cole, 1958 December 22; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 237)
- TLS Calkins to Cole, 1958 December 20; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 237)
- Telegram to Cole, 1958 December (Box 3, Folder 237)
- Telegram to Cole, undated (Box 3, Folder 238)
- TLS Cole to Father Tad, 1959 May 5; 2 pp. (Box 3, Folder 238)
- Cole from International Bank for Reconstruction and Development, 1958 January 7; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 238)
- TLS Ray to Cole, 1958 September 29; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 239)
- TLS Wainwright to Cole, 1958 September 29; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 239)
- TLS Cole to Taber, 1958 September 19; 1 p. (Box 3, Folder 239)
- Cole to Taber, undated; 1 p. (Box 4, Folder 240)
- TLS Taber to Cole, 1958 August 21; 1 p. (Box 4, Folder 240)
- TL Cole to Dorn, 1958 July 31; 1 p. (Box 4, Folder 240)
- TL Dorn to Cole, 1958 July 21; 1 p. (Box 4, Folder 240)
- TL Cole to Savage, 1958 March 14; 2 pp. (Box 4, Folder 241)
- Telegram Cole to Tom Cole, 1958 February 21 (Box 4, Folder 241)
- TLS Dempsey to Staff, 1957 November 18; 1 p. (Box 4, Folder 241)
- TLS Muirhead to Cole, 1958 January 16; 4 pp. (Box 4, Folder 242)
- TLS Tinkleman to Cole, 1959 March 25; 1 p. (Box 4, Folder 242)
- Personal letter, Jane and Dave to Cole, 1957 December 9; 1 p. (Box 4, Folder 242)
- TL George to Cole, 1960 April 10; 2 pp. and card (Box 4, Folder 243)
- Congressional Record-Senate, 1959; Pgs. 9273-9274. (Box 4, Folder 243)
- Cole to Honorable Sam Rayburn, 1957 October 8; 1 p. (Box 4, Folder 243)
- TL Cole to Secretary of State, New York, 1957 October 8; 1 p (Box 4, Folder 244)
- TL Cole to Hubbell, 1958 February 6; 1 p (Box 4, Folder 244)
- TL Hubbell to Cole, 1958 January 21 (Box 4, Folder 244)
- Songs and Humor, undated; 3 pp. (Box 4, Folder 245)
- Card, JC Staff to Cole, 1957 November 24; 1 p. (Box 4, Folder 245)
- Telegram Brobecks to Cole, 1957 November 24; 1 p. (Box 4, Folder 245)
- TLS Anderson to Joint Committee on Atomic Energy, 1957 November 19; 1 p. (Box 4, Folder 245)
- TLS Norris to Cole, 1957 December 12; 1 p. (Box 4, Folder 246 (1))
- Judgor for Hon. Sterling Cole, 1947 January 20; 1 p. (Box 4, Folder 246 (1))
- TLS Robert Cole to Cole, 1957 December 12; 1 p. (Box 4, Folder 246 (2))
- Unsigned note, 1957 November 25; 1 p. (Box 4, Folder 246 (2))
- TL Cole to Auchincloss, 1957 October 28; 1 p. (Box 4, Folder 247)
- TLS Roberts to Cole, 1957 October 26; 1 p. (Box 4, Folder 247)
- TL Cole to Roberts, 1957 August 15; 1 p. (Box 4, Folder 247)
- TL Cole to Roberts, 1957 October 23; 1 p. (Box 4, Folder 247)
- 547. Kunstauktion, 1960 March 17-19; Pgs. 1-80. (Box 4, Folder 248)
  With attached hand written note. (Art Auction Brochure).
- Bulletin of the Atomic Scientists, 1961 March; Pgs. 1-121. (Box 4, Folder 249)
- Eugene Rabinowitch, "Science and Party Platforms,"Bulletin of the Atomic Scientists XV, no. 10, 1959 December; Pgs. 405-409. (Box 4, Folder 250)
- "The Dawn of a New Decade,"Bulletin of the Atomic Scientists XVI No. 1, 1960 January; Pgs. 2-6. (Box 4, Folder 250)
- E. Rabinowitch, " First things First,"Bulletin of the Atomic Scientists Vol. XV, No. 9, 1959 November; Pgs. 361-365. (Box 4, Folder 251)
- S. de Madariaga, "Disarmament? The Problem Lies Deeper,"The New York Times Magazine, 1959 October 11; Pgs. 17, 72-76. (Box 4, Folder 252)
- TLS Strauss to Cole, 1957 March 7; 1 p. (2 copies) (Box 4, Folder 253)
- Types of Assistance which the Commission Announced it would Consider Offering under PROP, undated; 2 pp. (2 copies). (Box 4, Folder 253)
- TL Anderson to Green, 1957 March 22; 1 p. (Box 4, Folder 254)
- TL Green to Anderson, 1957 April 8; 1 p. (Box 4, Folder 254)
- Telegram Cole to Martin, 1957 September 23 (Box 4, Folder 254)
- TLS Starr to Cole, 1957 April 10; 1 p. (Box 4, Folder 255)
- TLS Cole to Durham, 1957 April 10; 5 pp. (Box 4, Folder 255)